

CONTACT



+91-9999123676



work.shubhamarora@gmail.com



www.shubhamarora.dev



New Delhi

SKILLS

- Cocoa Touch
- Swift
- Objective C
- Core Animation
- Multithreading & Concurrency
- Unit Testing

EDUCATION

Kurukshetra University 2015 - 2019 B.Tech

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi

SHUBHAM ARORA

IOS DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Over 3 years of experience in the area of iOS development, which includes understanding requirement specification, working on software design, coding testing and maintenance. Experienced in building Social, OTT and Financial iOS apps. In previous roles developed 7+ iOS apps that were downloaded by million users.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Paytm

iOS Developer Feb 2022 - Present

- I worked as an iOS developer in Paytm Money app of Paytm.
- I am core team member of Mutual Funds in Paytm Money.
- Worked in all aspects of iOS development for building new modules and revamping previous ones.
- Technologies and Architecture Swift, Objectve-C, MVVM + IO, RXCocoa, RxSwift

Bharti Airtel

iOS Developer May 2021 - February 2022

- Indian Multinational telecommunications service company.
- I was core team member of payment module in Airtel Thanks app.
- Worked in all aspects of iOS Development to build a Payment SDK which is now integrated in their all verticals.
- Technologies and Architecture Swift, Viper, Core Animation, Multithreading and Concurrency

99 Array

iOS Developer Intern June 2018 - October 2019 iOS Developer October 2019 - April 2021

- Noida based startup in the field of OTT Service Providers.
- Collaborated with 2 Engineers to build Watcho and Dialog ViU which has over 25 million downloaders.
- Lead the team for initial to final product of Nonton App.
- Technologies and Architecture Swift, Objective-C, MVVM, Multithreading and Concurency, Core Animation

RSVR Technologies

iOS Developer Intern May 2017 - June 2018

- Noida based startup in the field of IT Solution Providers. Created 1 app and maintained 3 apps.
- Created an app named MHG which act as a safety net for chronically ill patients by enabling them to monitor their conditions and triggering an emergency alarm in the case of acute abnormalities.
- Technologies and Architecture Swift, Objective-C, MVC, MVVM, Concurency